{
    "subject": "resource/Norman_Borlaug",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/surname",
    "object": "Borlaug",
    "human_readable": "The surname of Norman Borlaug is Borlaug.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864635467529297,
            "question": "What is the surname of Norman Borlaug?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8534497618675232,
            "question": "Is 'Borlaug' a common surname?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7362483739852905,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Norman Borlaug?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6900039315223694,
            "question": "What field is Norman Borlaug known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6037611961364746,
            "question": "In what countries did Norman Borlaug work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4270710349082947,
            "question": "Has Norman Borlaug won any notable awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4012811779975891,
            "question": "What are some of the challenges faced by agriculture today that Norman Borlaug addressed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34408625960350037,
            "question": "What impact did Norman Borlaug have on world food production?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3432115614414215,
            "question": "How did Norman Borlaug's work contribute to global food security?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.03337270766496658,
            "question": "Who is considered to be the 'Father of the Green Revolution'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The surname of Norman Borlaug is Borlaug.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6899_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did Norman Borlaug's work contribute to global food security?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6899_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What impact did Norman Borlaug have on world food production?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6899_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the challenges faced by agriculture today that Norman Borlaug addressed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6899_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_98.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6899_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents repeatedly state that Norman Borlaug's last name is Borlaug.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that \"Surname Borlaug\" and refer to multiple individuals with the last name Borlaug, including Norman Borlaug. Therefore, the statement that the surname of Norman Borlaug is Borlaug is supported by the provided context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}